infoline.com 2018-07-11

# Privacy Policy – Infoline.com

### Privacy Policy

Citizen Infoline Ltd. hereinafter referred to as “CIL” maintains the privacy of all the visitors to Infoline.com.

Any information collected from the website is used exclusively by “CIL” for marketing and promotional activities. The particulars that we collect are used as feedback to make the website more user-friendly and more informative. It also gives us an idea as to which service you visit the most, we try and improve on those links for you to understand “CIL” well and to make our web site's content and services more appropriate and easier to use. We may use the information provided by you, without prior permission, to send information about updates to our web site or other marketing resources.

We request all our users to read the following 'privacy policy' to understand how their personal & business information will be treated, as they make full use of our services to their benefit. This policy is applicable only to the entire network of marketplaces operated by CIL and not by any other company.

As a policy “CITIZEN” has never shared any information obtained on or from its web sites with any other organization and will not do so in future, unless required by law. “CITIZEN” has never sold any information obtained on this site to any party or parties external to “CIL” and its subsidiaries.

### Information we collect & how we collect it.

To provide you with information CIL may need information from you. CIL collects information from its users when they register to gain access to our services or at other specific instances when they are requested to provide us with their personal & business information. During registration, we ask the users for their name, email address, business information and other personal details. Once a user registers, he/she is no longer anonymous to Infoline.com and it is deemed that the user has given CIL the right to publish the desired business & personal details throughout its marketplaces, including but not limited to, Yellow Pages, business directory, trade leads, catalogs etc.

When you are on our network and are asked for personal information, you are sharing the information with CIL alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Promotions that run on our network may be sponsored by companies other than CIL or may be co-sponsored by CIL and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. However, you can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared.

We also gather usage statistics such as pages viewed, number of unique visitors, browser software, screen resolution etc. for analysis that helps us provide you improved user experience and services.

### Use of Personal & Business Information

Infoline.com's primary goal in collecting personal or public information is to provide the user with a customized experience on our network of sites. This includes personalized services, interactive communication and other services, most of which are completely free and remaining are paid. Business information is used to display the user's business listing or product offerings across our network to fetch maximum business opportunities for the user. 

In order to provide free services, CIL displays advertisements based upon the site usage statistics and visitor trends. CIL uses user's personal & business information to serve targeted advertisements through its websites, newsletters and customized mailers. In addition to it, once the user's personal and business information is displayed on our network, the user may start receiving business enquiries through email, phone calls or SMS notifications, from various buyers and sellers that might or might not be of their interest. CIL does not exercise any control over its users for sending business inquiries to the listed members. 

We record buying and browsing activities of our users including but not limited to their client's contact details and profiles and uses the same to provide value-added services to our users. 

### With whom we may Share or distribute your Information

We may need to share your information with other organizations to provide you with our Services or information you ask for.

We may share your information as follows or as otherwise described in this privacy policy:   
\- with other companies in the Citizen Group  
\- with vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf.  
\- with data processing companies, mailing houses and other third party suppliers working on our behalf;  
\- in response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;  
\- in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company;  
with your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information; and  
\- with other third parties in limited circumstances such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud and protecting the rights, property and safety of CIL and our users. 

### How do we keep your Information Secure

We take the security of your personal information seriously. CIL takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

### Updation of Information

We limit our collection of information about you to that which is relevant for the intended business and legal purposes for which it is to be used. We do not use information about you in a way that is incompatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by you. To the extent necessary for those purposes, we take steps to ensure that information about you is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and current.

You have the right to review and update your personal details. You can send us a request by email or a letter to our correspondence address. We will delete your information at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. Because of the way we maintain certain Services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

We will ask you to identify yourself and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

The policy may change from time to time so please check periodically.

If you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies; please send us an email at support@infoline.com
